

Iurov Timofei

Role: Junior Other Delivery Specialist Specialization: Software - Other Location: St. Petersburg

About me

I'm a hardworking and a level-headed person with a great desire to develop in IT sphere. I'm experienced in programming and ready to be hired as a frontend developer.

Skills

Hard skills

HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, React, JSON, XML, Git, GitLab, TypeScript, Angular, Express.JS, JSON Web Token (JWT), KnexJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Node.js, NoSQL, PostgreSQL, Redux, SQL

Soft skills

Presentation Skills **Public Speaking** Time management Decision-making skills Critical thinking Stress management

Work Experience

Junior Developer

IT1 | Jan 2021 - Present Russia, St. Petersburg JSON, XSD, XML, Page-Proofs

AIESEC Leadership Development Program

Jan 2018 - Mar 2018 Czech Republic, Ostrava Educated students in schools

Project Manager, Electrical Engineer

Akrit Engineering | Sep 2016 - Aug 2017 Russia, St. Petersburg

Team organization, contracts with suppliers, creating of the final product

Languages Spoken

Russian - Proficient English - Advanced Spanish - Elementary Czech - Beginner

Education

Saint-Petersburg Electrotechnical University ETU "LETI"

2013 - 2017

Bachelor, Nanotechnology and microsystems engineering.

Get in touch!

Mobile:

+7 911 752-24-08



Email:

tim.riene@gmail.com

Training Courses

Upper-Intermediate English May 2012